this tutorial is about exploiting away
本教程是关于利用
平行折叠在打开时移动
this tutorial is about exploiting away
parallel fold to move as you open close
传播这是您的例子
打开它，花就会打开，你可以看到
parallel fold to move as you open close
the spread here's the example as you
它的工作方式有一个花梗
粘在脊椎上，它就会出现
the spread here's the example as you
open it the flower opens and you can see
通过空心给你空心管
然后连接到此平行折叠
open it the flower opens and you can see
the way it works there's a flower stem
当它关闭时，脊椎褶皱就消失了
向下和顶部平行折叠
the way it works there's a flower stem
is stuck to the spine and it comes up
出现并且整个事情都打开了
脊椎褶皱出现，平行
is stuck to the spine and it comes up
through a hollow to you the hollow tube
折叠下降，这是机制
将该运动转移到
through a hollow to you the hollow tube
is then attached to this parallel fold
花，这是很新的
机制，但有两三本书
is then attached to this parallel fold
and as it closes the spine fold goes
我会告诉你的
我想告诉你的第一个是
and as it closes the spine fold goes
down and the top of the parallel fold
David Pellom的足迹
这是一本非常美丽的书
down and the top of the parallel fold
comes up and as the whole thing opens
用白色做，花在这里
中间，当它打开时，您会看到
comes up and as the whole thing opens
the spine fold comes up and the parallel
花开了，如果你看着它结束
你会看到有来的茎
the spine fold comes up and the parallel
fold goes down and so it's the mechanism
贯穿整个中间
平行折叠非常花哨，
fold goes down and so it's the mechanism
transfers that movement to the top of
那么你会有更多的平行折叠
顶部和柜台折叠整个
transfers that movement to the top of
the flower and it's quite a new
事情真的很壮观
第二个是妮娜（Nina）的Leola变色龙
the flower and it's quite a new
mechanism but there's two or three books
connieyc，在这种情况下，它不是
花开了，是火烈鸟传播
mechanism but there's two or three books
that I'll show you that have it in so
它的翅膀和整个结构是
在这里，它很小
that I'll show you that have it in so
the first one I'd like to show you is
这些漂浮的睡莲伪装成
平行折叠，如果我们看着它并完成
the first one I'd like to show you is
trail by David Pellom
你可以看到有一只鹳
中间，这就是主体
trail by David Pellom
it's a really beautiful book this all
打开时，火烈鸟就附着在上面
并关闭它，鸟打开它归零
it's a really beautiful book this all
done in white and the flower is here in
翅膀，最后一个是纸花
由雷·马歇尔（Ray Marshall）发表
done in white and the flower is here in
the middle and as it opens you see the
不同的是，花朵没有那么高
茎全部都在同一根上工作
the middle and as it opens you see the
flower open and if you look at it end on
原则是中间有茎
推开花中间
flower open and if you look at it end on
you can see there's the stalk that comes
然后在外面拉那些碎片
它把所有的花朵都弄下来了
you can see there's the stalk that comes
up through the middle and all the the
内置在教程的表带上
九随着页面放平
up through the middle and all the the
parallel fold is extremely fancy and
弹出窗口相当平坦，它
偏心地创建这些沟渠，然后
parallel fold is extremely fancy and
then you've got more parallel folds on
然后将这两朵花内置
那些沟渠使这些
then you've got more parallel folds on
the top and counter folds the whole
如果你看着中央沟
最后，您可以看到有一个
the top and counter folds the whole
thing is really quite spectacular the
支柱上升，中间上升
花的中间，然后有
thing is really quite spectacular the
second one is Leola chameleon by Nina
外边缘的碎片拉下
花的外缘，所以我现在
second one is Leola chameleon by Nina
connieyc and in this case it's not a
只是做一个，所以我们从一张脸开始
片
connieyc and in this case it's not a
flower opening it's a flamingo spreading
折叠好后的褶皱非常彻底
然后这是要去的那一块
flower opening it's a flamingo spreading
its wings and the whole structure is
成为我中间的茎
使它厚几层
its wings and the whole structure is
down here it's pretty small slightly
事先已经打了分数，所以我可以
只是把它折起来就放胶水了
down here it's pretty small slightly
disguised by these floating water lilies
测量了它我已经切好了
底部的襟翼顶部的襟翼
disguised by these floating water lilies
parallel fold if we look at it and done
这些是我们会坚持下去的
这些都是基础
parallel fold if we look at it and done
you can see there is a stork comes up
贴在花上，我已经测量
所以我把折痕放到了
you can see there is a stork comes up
the middle and that's the body of the
会在那里坚持脊柱
您可以看到整个内容的顶部
the middle and that's the body of the
flamingos attached to that as you open
将会来到这里，在那里
花要粘上，所以我们会
flamingos attached to that as you open
and close it the bird open zeroes it
首先将其粘上并粘上
放到脊椎上，所以把所有的都折叠
and close it the bird open zeroes it
wings and the last one is paper blossoms
衬衫，这是库存
这将上升到中间
wings and the last one is paper blossoms
by Ray Marshall this is slightly
有两个襟翼
按钮，我们将其粘贴到
by Ray Marshall this is slightly
differently flowers aren't on such high
脊柱
这样管子就和脊柱齐平了
differently flowers aren't on such high
stalks all of them work on the same
这是平行折叠
越过顶端，这就是事实
stalks all of them work on the same
principle there's a stalk up the middle
每侧都有一个标签，
中间有一个洞，可以让鹳走
principle there's a stalk up the middle
pushing up the middle of the flower and
通过，所以只需检查那是
将像这些折叠
pushing up the middle of the flower and
then those pieces on the outside pulling
在下面，所以我会把它们都粘在
同时将遵循该方法
then those pieces on the outside pulling
it down all the flowers on this have
将这些粘着的一面朝下
首先，然后让另一个人找到
it down all the flowers on this have
built onto the strap which is tutorial
它的自然位置
有一个我将其全部折叠成
built onto the strap which is tutorial
nine that as the page goes flat
平仓
关闭底座，以便知道要放哪里
nine that as the page goes flat
the pop-up goes fairly flat and it
我会做的袖子
过去了，所以他们需要
the pop-up goes fairly flat and it
creates these gullies off-center and
分数线我只是一折线
并确保将其整齐地折叠成一个
creates these gullies off-center and
then these two flowers are built into
管，然后在底部，这是
它会附在哪里
then these two flowers are built into
that those gullies these run that
平行折叠，所以我们将其折叠
层并取出其中之一，所以
that those gullies these run that
working on the central gully if you look
底部只有两个襟翼
袖子这将要点击
working on the central gully if you look
at it end on you can see there's a
我们需要测量的茎高
这快到把它切成那个
at it end on you can see there's a
pillar goes up the middle raises the
到达那里的点确保
它冲在那里并切开
pillar goes up the middle raises the
middle of the flower and then there's
到这里，我要再切一块
关闭，所以只剩下两个襟翼
middle of the flower and then there's
pieces on the outer edges pull down the
削减到这里
并拆分到这里，所以有两个
pieces on the outer edges pull down the
outer edges of the flower so now I'll
拍打，我们可以将其粘上
多胶水
outer edges of the flower so now I'll
just make one so we start with a face
现在坐在袖子上
我只是想把它戳开
just make one so we start with a face
sheet
它有点安定或容易工作否
你们都把这两个粘在了
sheet
well folded creased really thoroughly
平行折叠
哦，是的，这些现在要漂浮了
well folded creased really thoroughly
and then this is the piece that's going
回到这是我们可以的花片
粘在我们制作的皮瓣上
and then this is the piece that's going
to be the stalk up the middles I'm
茎的顶部
当这平坦的时候，这些将会来
to be the stalk up the middles I'm
making it several layers thick I've
加入它，所以您现在需要
将折痕添加到
making it several layers thick I've
scored it already beforehand so I can
适合顶部的花朵，所以
你那里一个，这里一个
scored it already beforehand so I can
just fold it up put glue in I've also
检查高度是否正确
总的来说，但是你会得到
just fold it up put glue in I've also
measured it I've cut it so it's got
想法，现在我们将这些粘贴到
花在它的打开位置
measured it I've cut it so it's got
flaps at the bottom flaps at the top so
平直的，我们只是胶水
那然后我们需要等待一个
flaps at the bottom flaps at the top so
these are the ones that we'll stick it
分钟胶水脱落，因为
然后，我们将关闭整个过程
these are the ones that we'll stick it
to the base these are the ones that will
这两个小件满足需求
折叠它们，以便我们将整个封闭
to the base these are the ones that will
stick it to the flower and I've measured
的东西，它将找到其自然的地方
在我这样做之前，我只会说你
stick it to the flower and I've measured
it so I've put the crease where it's
可以在此书弹出窗口中了解更多信息
设计和纸张力学，但有
it so I've put the crease where it's
going to stick to the spine there and
关于它的机制
还有各种各样其他有趣的事情
going to stick to the spine there and
you can see the top of the whole thing
东西，所以现在运气好了
足够远，我们可以将其关闭并制作
you can see the top of the whole thing
is going to come here that's where the
确保这些褶皱会在
你去的正确地方
is going to come here that's where the
flower is going to stick on so we'll
您